Three years ago, we started on a journey
to respond to [music] the talent
challenges out there and build the next
generation of Business Central talent.
And we're proud of the impact it's had
on people's [music] lives, their
careers, and your business. We've
onboarded more than 700 new
professionals with a 91% [music]
retention rate billable in 10 weeks. And
senior staff can save up [music] to 80%
of their time not having to train
juniors.
But the world's changing fast. AI is
reshaping [music] every product,
experience, and profession, including
ours. But don't worry, AI won't replace
your people. [music] But the right
people with AI skills will. At VC
Talent, we help you futureproof your
team.
>> And how will you do that?
>> Oh, um,
>> let me take it from here. We've got
three ways to help you become an AI
powerhouse. To [music] create autonomous
AI agents, you need people who
understand industry and business
processes and can blend that with AI
[music] fluency.
>> And most importantly, you need to think
about AI [music] proving the people you
already have, the dinosaurs who have
helped you build your business success.
And then [music] there's Gen Z. You
know, the people who speak AI. We can
help them turn that knowledge into
business central expertise. so you can
hire [music] them. One thing's clear,
the future won't wait. We know [music]
change is tough, but you're not alone.
So, what's it going to [music] be?
Watching from the sidelines or joining
the movement?
>> Come and talk to us. [laughter]